Assalamualaikum warrahmatullahi wabarakatuh
waalaikumsalam warrahmatullahi wabarakatuh
Thank you Siti Azizah for coming. Before that, can you introduce yourself first? Your name and your hobby.
Ya, Greetings from me. I'm Siti Azizah, I'm studying in UIN Jakarta, majority of Accountant.
My hobby is sports and i like teaching.
But, before that, may I ask you, do you like reading or writing?
Hmm, reading a book, quite good, but I can't say I'm addicted to reading.
And, for writing, I used to like it, but for now, I don't write very often. I mean, I haven't started yet
okay
there is an application called storyou. This is a final assignment of Mobile Computing course
This application is for people who want to share their stories or book reviews. And this application is almost similar to the medium application
For the features of this application, there are login, register, create stories, read stories and get notifications when new stories come in.
And before continuing to the point, wanna ask something?
For example, if you want to make a story, are there any terms and conditions? such as the length of the words or what is the theme of stories like a short story or just a book review or is it up to me?
Ya, no conditions. It's up to the writer. If likened, this is like a blog. The author writes the title and the story. You can write anything.
But, not like a novel. Because novels have many chapters. And, for this application, just cant write one story..
okay okay
mantul
okay, maybe we can start to try this application. can you share the screen?
oke wait
did it show up?
yes..
Have you registered before?
Not yet.
Okey, you must register/signup first.
"Siti azizah is doing account registration"
wait, I can't, cin..
What happened? You can't register?
Yeah
Ooh, you still in login page, Azizah.. Go to....
Ooh, signup page ya,,
Yeah, you can input random password, it doesn't have to be the same as your google account
Okay
"Siti Azizah is creating account again"
Done...
Nah, this is home page of Storyou App.. And
Oh, When you logged in, you couldn't, right, because we haven't created an account yet, maybe we can try to login. Siti, can you log out first and login again :D
Go to the profile page, zah.
"Siti azizah logout his account"
Nah, now, you can login using your account
Done..
You can choose a story to read
Wait? This is?? haha
Haha, this is an example display of story haha.
ooh okey
Is this going to be like Wattpad or not?
Noo, different. Wattpad has many chapters right? And this application, more like a blog, you just can create one story
hoo, hoalah. okeoke
Oh, create a book review, can't I?
Yes, you can..
Okay, you can create content or story..
Azizah : Create content ya?
Cindi : He eh
Hmm, I filling the first field yah?
Yeah, and for now, you just can input URL images on the web/internet for the cover content/story.
Link source image yah?
The title is the "Judul" of story/book/content, right?
Yes, you are right.
Sorry, why, in my HP can't scroll and rotate ya?
Waduh.
"Azizah still create content."
Done, it's just an example ya.
oh, please input the URL image first.
Okay, I'm searching in google ya
"Siti Azizah searching the relevant Image"
Like this?
You can copy the image URL, zah.
Okey, done
But, wait,
I can't see button "create". just a red line.
Maybe, I made a mistake while creating the display interface. I make it less responsive
Because in my HP, don't have a problem..
So, does that mean you can write a story, right? but, there is a problem with the button create.
yaa
Okey, next, we will try the last feature, there is notification. Please, close your the app.
Will the notification appear?
"Cindi trying to create content to test a feature"
Is there a notification?
Yes...
Okay, so the notification is already ya?
Okay, maybe it's enough.
But, before we finish this meeting, do you have anything to say?
Hmm, for this item, is there no picture?
Ohh, for that item,
Oh ya cin, there is "recomendation, education, popular etc"
Its, cannot clicked ya?
Yes, for now, it cannot be clicked. And the feature just login, register, create a story, read a story and notification.
And, actually, The initial plan of making this will also have a favourite menu, but it is not finished. hehe.
Okey, no problem.
This is your project?
Yes, my class. We have mobile computing course and this is a Final Project from that course.
is there a review or not from you?
It's cool
This is a team project?
No, this is an individual project
So is this a client request or what?
Oh, no. This is a final project. We are free to choose any idea. And in the lecturer's acc. And, I want to make this kind of application. Because I like reading and writting too
Over all, its good. The feature already run. Not error.
And also, maybe, the interface less symmetrical
Iya ya, maybe because of different HP.
This is the same, the criticism is, on my cellphone the buttons are just lines.
How can this be rotated?
Rotate? Hmm, let's try..
Oh ya, it can..
Try to create the page, it's same? Can it be scrolled?
Yes, cannot be scrolled..
Okeh, good, cin. Hopefully this application can add more some features. And become a bigger app hehe
And I see this app, like a Wattpad ya? but it's more towards making a review, right?
Thank you Azizah for taking the time to do this user testing Storyou App
Yourwelcome
Good luck to all Zizah.
May be, we can finish meeting session for today. More or less, I said sorry wassalamualaikum warrahmatullahi wabarakatuh
Waalaikumsalam Warrahmatullah Wabarakatuh